<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Handy Voice</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>

    <string name="nav_item_welcome">Welcome/Courses</string>
    <string name="nav_item_news_and_updates">Login</string>
    <string name="nav_item_blog">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="nav_item_about">About US</string>

    <!-- navigation drawer item labels  -->
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_labels">
        <item>@string/nav_item_welcome</item>
        <item>@string/nav_item_news_and_updates</item>
        <item>@string/nav_item_blog</item>
        <item>@string/nav_item_about</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_welcome">Welcome/Courses</string>
    <string name="title_about">About Us</string>
    <string name="title_signup">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="title_login">Login</string>
    <string name="question">\?</string>




    <!-- Documentation -->

        <string name="intro_documentation">HTML (HyperText Markup Language) is the most basic building
            block of the Web. It describes and defines the content of a webpage along with the basic
            layout of the webpage. Other technologies besides HTML are generally used to describe a
            web page\'s appearance/presentation (CSS) or functionality/ behavior (JavaScript).</string>




    <string name="content_documentation">HTML (HyperText Markup Language) is the most basic building
        block of the Web. It describes and defines the content of a webpage along with the basic
        layout of the webpage. Other technologies besides HTML are generally used to describe a web
        page\'s appearance/presentation (CSS) or functionality/ behavior (JavaScript).
        "HyperText" refers to links that connect web pages to one another, either within a single
        website or between websites. Links are a fundamental aspect of the Web. By uploading
        content to the Internet and linking it to pages created by other people, you become an
        active participant in the World Wide Web.
        HTML uses "markup" to annotate text, images, and other content for display in a Web browser.
        HTML markup includes special "elements" such as head , title, body, header, footer, article, section, p, div,
        span, img, and many others.
        Tags in HTML are case insensitive. That is, they can be written in uppercase, lowercase,
        or a mixture. Example title tag can be written as Title,TiTlE or in any other way.</string>



    <string name="Testing_documentation">
    This module explores how to use HTML to include multimedia in your web pages, including the
        different ways that images can be included, and how to embed video, audio, and even entire
        other webpages.
    Representing tabular data on a webpage in an understandable, accessible way can be a challenge.
        This module covers basic table markup, along with more complex features such as implementing
        captions and summaries.
    Forms are a very important part of the Web — these provide much of the functionality you need
        for interacting with websites, e.g. registering and logging in, sending feedback, buying
        products, and more. This module gets you started with creating the client-side/front-end
        parts of forms.
    Provides links to sections of content explaining how to use HTML to solve very common problems
        when creating a web page: dealing with titles, adding images or videos, emphasizing content,
        creating a basic form, etc.</string>






    <string name="summary_documentation">This module sets the stage, getting you used to important
        concepts and syntax such as looking at applying HTML to text, how to create hyperlinks,
        and how to use HTML to structure a web page.</string>
    <!-- Documentation string ends -->
    <!-- Strings to change the mode -->
    <string name="menu_night_mode">Change the mode</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_system">Follow system</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_day">Day (always)</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_night">Night (always)</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="Color">TextColor</string>
    <string name="learn_to_communicate_with_deaf_people">Learn to communicate with deaf people</string>
    <string name="for_entreprises">For Entreprises</string>
    <string name="courses_for_deaf">Courses for deaf</string>


</resources>
